All right.
Call or the regular schedule meeting of my city council for Tuesday August 19, 2020, 5.
I'll give it or I'll just get it in personal classes.
We have none.
Three claims list.
Who's your proof?
Hi.
Don't fall high.
Joan.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Four.
Minutes for the August 5, 2020, 5.
Are you ready?
No.
I'm sorry.
Joan.
I'm so sorry.
Correct.
Five.
Discussion on veterans, they've brain to get over Sunday, November 9, 2025.
We'll start with the Berthord and the Schnell ladies.
Congratulations.
I'm sorry.
Truly the people that have been jeeks.
I've always been the sticky part for a day and eat.
Oh we're well done another day right there.
They inferred.
They made this anyway, and I've just beenбу.
You've just been with well people who are like fruits, but they wanted to break.
A look like you're going to have a Zimmerate.
Another reason I'll end this to the Sun they after knew we'd become scorer for the test flight.
This way here we don't interfere with it.
Starting with the shooting now.
Decoration hours.
We do that opportunity that our Bank Bay is that one little for people,
on age pre, so they don't, but we're trying to wanted to tap them before that we've got
a car on the right to the middle of the door.
So, our chiefs here, so you guys want to talk to him here in a minute.
Is there any problems you can't speak to?
You can't speak to him here in a minute.
So, I got your contact.
And again, thank you for being as productive as it is.
It gives us a lot of room to work.
Thank you.
Thank you guys for your service.
Thank you for your service.
We're going to have trucks and stuff in the left hand frame.
Usually, the city has before the city will have a fire truck,
and we have the utility trucks in there.
So, if the city has stuff, if we can know when, what are what people do I can get?
and why didn't we have a kind of a wide-up where we tried to stagger the right, be able to
group in the parade. We don't have old bands in one spot, the horses out front. So I guess you
guys would get what they would do. If they want to be in the parade, they can get a hold of the
the elk, or get a hold of me, I'm feeling like I'm a pretty popular guy anymore. And we can
never do this in the parade or why have we to be all of this? Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Thanks, I also just don't. I think six resolutions, CC-2025-10, supporting continuing
participation in the Main Street Program, Tender.
Good evening. I come before you to request the signature of Mayor Parker for the Resolution by the
City Council. For the city of Miami, Oklahoma, supporting the continued participation of the Main Street.
This is a yearly resolution. Contact at the state now, there is program.
Tamara Nelson. She more support of it, but from the way we handle our Main Street Program in Miami than
this very quick. Yes. Yes. Absolutely. She's coming to town next Wednesday. She's coming to town.
We'll have an opportunity to meet her and we'll make friends.
Madam, Ms. Merrick, when in support of how we handle our Main Street Program here, so hopefully the
new lady is, so I mean, I mean, a lot to us. No, who put your mouth no more?
What? What do you have to do? What do you have to do for me?
I'll make a motion difference.
Thank you. Thank you, President.
Thank you, President.
This question of possible action regarding proposed transfer of property,
locate the 2017 denorties to the Miami special utility authority.
Here's a potential for some.
Sorry.
The one signs is interested in the property.
And for the city. So I talked to Ken Williams about transaction if we went from MSUA to the city.
It should be transferred to the UMSUA.
Is it that big property route beside the old AT&T building?
Yeah, they tore it out.
Can you share their houses there?
There will be four city houses. They're just there.
Right. So there's some covenants that are going to run with that property.
There's not a lot that can be done with it.
Therefore, it's not worth a lot as money.
And he's already bought the old AT&T property.
So this would do me a joint.
Jones, thank you.
He said that.
So far.
Perfect.
Thank you.
Faith.
Cooperative agreement between the Miametri of Oklahoma and the city.
Miamet from Bridge.
119.29.
Replacement project.
Located on West.
Veterans Boulevard between Main Street and G.
So is everybody knows I love large projects.
I love like a stranded make mime and better with some large infrastructure projects.
So this is a cooperation agreement between us and the Miametri.
For a new bridge on 22nd.
So this is directly by the West of the warehouse.
The plans are actually in your packet.
So at first came to the city.
That bridge was redesigned.
And then nothing really came about of it.
So I was thinking one day like, hey, we should go after some project for the bridge.
And so I pulled up the old plans.
Started talking to the Miametri of the program.
They had similar to.
If it really knows, we have the central main bridge.
You know, the chief of the quick bridge.
You know, it was paid for by travel funds.
This is a different program.
But you know, in the same thought process.
So this is about to an at me and learn bridge.
So it was part of the cooperation agreement.
We would design the bridge.
Have environmental stuff done.
And then you know, paider to locate any relocating utilities.
And then they would, you know, submit the grant application to do that.
So this is the first day.
So we'd submit for the funding.
And then if it proved, then we'd bring another agreement back to the board.
Like, who's got a major project?
Who's got a major money?
It's like that.
So when we did it with the auto.
We made the project in the money.
You know, Missy does have one of this glamour to bring in.
Any time that you go into a agreement with a tribe, it's a contract.
There's no prison disagreement over who's going to manage the project, have the money's
going to be spent, or stuck with mediation or arbitration, or their court.
In some circumstances, we might be able to get into the budget.
It's about to do that, I mean, the county's doing a project, right now.
I say we still approve this phase of it, and that it gets as long as there's no money
exchange to them to contract your written and drawn up.
Motioner critical points.
Jones, type of a worker, foreign, five, each step.
Aye.
Double pie.
Nine or minutes, 2025, that's zero seven, a mending section, 21, that's 20, it's Article 2.
From chapter 21 of the Code of Wardens is providing severability.
And establishing a effective date for mending right away, excavation report.
So this is what we previously talked about.
This is like we're trying to just get up a really, really strong ordinance for this.
I will put it on next Tuesday and next meeting.
Which to approve?
No, no, no.
No action.
This is action.
I don't know.
I already send my motion.
I don't approve.
And update discussion on completed and upcoming street projects.
This is also a big packet for us.
That will fix the speed.
No, no.
Don't carry it up.
You can do it.
What about the one on F?
Yes.
Okay, set it down in New South East.
This part was between the 18th and the 18th.
Again, the water was good, but at the end it's a total reconstruction.
We're doing this with you, man.
Next block from New South East to New South East.
My research is not intersection.
And so it's nice to see that works.
We've done that area of town because those roads are really bad up in there.
And so I know for them and everybody on that street there,
they're extremely happy with the work that you guys have done.
So thank you.
I say fabulous.
This is for us.
We're going to work as a street.
It's also going to be in a parking lot.
We're going to take a little further.
I heard a lot of positives about it too.
I heard a lot of people in that area that are businesses and business owners.
Very useful that we took care of that problem.
First line is a small section that was taken in the middle.
I remember that.
So, this little quick story on this street, we got called out there by a resident when they
a man Brian Tyler met out there and his road was horrible and not many people live on
that street but he was a bad shape and the guy was changing the flat tire and his driveway
because one of the rocks in the road and causing the flat but you know what, he came over
and said I appreciate because he was coming out like this thing at your time because it was
late the evening when we went out there but I'm glad to see it got done because a lot of
times people in this road said they were saying you know we know there's one three or four
houses here so you guys don't care about us. We do, we're here so if you get to see it get done.
It was bad and thank you all here. We've not packed that whole area in there.
Halfway three made a big improvement by taking all the old stuff and just making it a grower
road for a bit.
That was, we actually looked at it from the underlier, but this is the point how the street car
built and they've got a big intersection at the car field and we're going to just be going to call
on that one like a four clock today.
So at 24, we have an eye southwest, plan to do a, well, if you're
probably going to, I'm just reading those for full transparency.
I do a family that lives up to three hundred, one of the two speakers that
have been there, who's been living there.
One of them making some comment sections.
And they're all going to be really nice by our houses.
So this goes right now.
This will be right for me.
We just read the next thing we're going to do is, we're going to
play in the mass hall.
This will be able to point more back to 20.
This will be, you know, the state just did, this part of 20 is
the board, which is done.
So the wall is the, where the T is.
We, we used to use out the 24.
It does.
Oh, okay.
That's the T is small section.
There's the county.
But then you're going to the county.
You're going to do it all of 66 there.
So the travel are next year for the Centennial becoming,
but closely the whole section.
And then the city streets were there.
So it would be kind of cool.
You get the highway.
You know, I would be nice and like.
Okay.
So with these projects here, this is why we have them.
So what can we do?
That big open areas would be as well.
We can like, on car.
The reason we.
We.
So the other thing with this project I said that the other reason we're going to point that I get a digital copy of this
I text that I emailed Jeff to see if you send
I've got somebody I love to send that you
Good work
This is this issue it is for my partner. I'll personally want to thank you for all you do for us
Because every time I have to call somebody and I call you you're up there. Thank you
Before you leave
I agree Kevin
I send the text message to Tyler and Robert man. They're on and they get a thing here
I'll leave pass on with the citizens brought to me
So that addresses the concern that it's quite like so
Congratulations, and you as they all get a response back saying thank you before I get a response back to you been there
So we appreciate you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Do you step Jones?
I firm.
I don't.
I.
Well, mayor's nomination to point Doug Hubelson to the airport board
in replacing Jeff Hau, current expire 1177.
Burns?
I.
He stepped.
Hi.
Thank you.
Art.
I'm saying.
I'm just kidding.
Missy.
I won't be the first time.
I'm just kidding.
There are 10 new business.
If any was the difference, it's supposed to misadivit.
14 staff reports.
15 mayor.
We have a great fair, last week people out there are a lot of activity and you pretty
observe.
I think every kid there at the time, so I've got at least $1,000 for their animals.
So we've got some really good, we've got the rodeo coming up this weekend, so still a lot
of that stuff going on, but I appreciate everything that the city does because the parent
wouldn't have been pulled off.
The rodeo wouldn't be pulled off without all you got to do extra stuff, so thank you.
Thank you.
We appreciate it.
16.
What's your name?
It's been good.
Travis wanted to remind everybody that we are going to have the demolition
of the Cormand Auto for the Metinay and Montzette Timber's third.
Yeah, I'm not following that.
It's going to be in the start, it's a kick off, I've been in the demo and some properties
that I heard.
Are you using dynamite?
Characters.
I'm going to give a track how I do that.
Oh, yeah, this is driving the track.
It's all that down the road.
I don't know if I can pizza it's cold in here.
No, no, no, no, no, that's all I have, it's going to make the border wear.
It's at the third, can I end this one?
Okay.
He might put this all on there.
I'm setting a alarm.
We might need it, just let's see what else can you pedal, see what I mean.
It's fine.
Look at Derek.
This has a, yeah.
That's a Tim, the toolman, Taylor, feel about it.
Everybody gets the biggest wife. Is that what they're saying all right 17 adjournment. Oh, wait
We got thank you, card
Don't read says dear mom's counsel your kindness. So appreciate it. Thank you so much for the amazing
Ethel put no order to present to us during the air and festival
We're so proud and honored we love the Ethel and we'll try to live up to the honor
David and then we each
So I